



CONTACT



Phone

+37256804966



robbegarm@gmail.com



Address

Maleva Põik 6, Tallinn, Estonia



EDUCATION

2018 - 2020 **Master Of Science** in Engineering TalTech University

2012 - 2018 **Bachelor Of Physics** Yerevan State University



COURSES

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

React JS Udemy

Udemy

Udemy

TypeScript Udemy



LANGUAGES

C1 C1



ABOUT ME

Highly self-motivated frontend developer with experience in designing, building, and deploying real-world websites. I am very passionate about programming and the web and have learned the necessary skills through multiple online courses. I am interested in a junior frontend developer position.



WORK EXPERIENCE

> Fullstack Web Developer 11.2022 - current E-Pavement OÜ, Estonia

- · Website and UI design, SEO and deployment
- · Building the frontend using React JS
- Building the backend with Spring Boot(Java)/MySQL
- > Solar Panel Engineer 06.2020 - current E-Pavement OÜ, Estonia
 - Production of solar panels, quality control
 - · Electronics development, PCB soldering
 - Installation, repair and on-site maintenance work
- Frontend Web Developer 08.2022 - 11.2022 Khnami, Estonia (remote)
 - · Website design, SEO and deployment
 - · Building the website with React JS
- > Robot Operator 03.2020 - 06.2020 Starship OÜ, Estonia
 - · Overseeing delivery robots using special software
 - · Remote operation, logging and reporting of issues

MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

BACKEND WEB FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPMENT DEVELOPMENT HTML5/CSS3 Java/ Spring Boot JavaScript (ES6) **REST API development** React JS MySQL TypeScript



SOFT SKILLS

- ✓ Fast learner
- √ Team player
- Problem solver
- Critical thinker
- √ Time management
- ✓ Self-management

PORTFOLIO

GitHub

www.github.com/RobBegArm

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/robbegarm/